{
    "id": "00d284a97a3d4467b18de4fd447ee9f5",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "‘I haven’t paid the fee.’ ‘I haven’t ……………………’",
            "description": "After a negative remark we can express another negative remark with neither or not either.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "also",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7ce85877b5a4d0183ccc3f062cc9c1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ………………………… daughter is a pilot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a11c8f51c961448e8b3891b792f41b62"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her husband is ten years ………………………… than her.",
            "description": "Elder and eldest can only be used before nouns (attributively).",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12758341db3a443c9d06d561ed92e5f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Nice movie?’ ‘ ………………………………, it was a complete waste of time.’",
            "description": "We use on the contrary to contradict a suggestion/opinion made by another speaker.",
            "answers": [
                "By contrast",
                "On the other hand",
                "On the contrary"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cde7ffe8d4b44859948cbcae017087e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train was late. ………………………….. this, we managed to reach on time.",
            "description": "We can use in spite of to introduce something which sounds surprising in view of what was said before.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "300a18a8088d490b89ccc8f9d96b2f4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she is eighty, she enjoys ………………………………",
            "description": "We do not normally use articles with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "a good health",
                "good health"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ba20262237e483a87006022f17fc0aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ………………………… for the job.",
            "description": "When enough is an adjective, it goes before the noun it modifies.",
            "answers": [
                "experience enough",
                "enough experience"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12d8fcd94d674d81929722e5158b0612"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no question of …………………………. resigning from the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4306d68173e34a828d70706744c51558"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you dare …………………………. your mind to the test?",
            "description": "When dare is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "put",
                "to put",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee40999d97274e14bb7c26b4f6dc796c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you bought the …………………………?",
            "description": "Groceries is not normally used in the plural form. ",
            "answers": [
                "grocery",
                "groceries"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e626493e95843a294414a81e96f3303"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can I give you a lift?’ ‘No thanks, I would prefer ………………………….’",
            "description": "We use a to-infinitive after would prefer.",
            "answers": [
                "walk",
                "to walk",
                "walking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1ea6b4c9c12741e0adc3da8e05865403"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate ………………………….. at weekends.",
            "description": "After hate, both infinitives and ing forms can be used.",
            "answers": [
                "working",
                "to work",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e7d853836ea40478fad5e79e42dfd20"
        }
    ]
}